[
    {
        "sender": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934ca",
        "recipient": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934ca",
        "question": "How many stars does the New Zealand national flag have?",
        "answer": "Four",
        "answered": true,
        "isAnonymous": true
    },
    {
        "sender": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934cc",
        "recipient": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934ca",
        "question": "The zodiac sign 'Pisces' refers to what animal?",
        "answer": "Fish",
        "answered": true
    },
    {
        "sender": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934cc",
        "recipient": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934cb",
        "question": "What is the fear of light flashes called?",
        "answer": "Selaphobia",
        "answered": true,
        "isAnonymous": true
    },
    {
        "sender": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934cd",
        "recipient": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934cb",
        "question": "What year did designer Manolo Blahnik open his first namesakes store in Hong Kong?",
        "answer": "1991",
        "answered": true
    },
    {
        "sender": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934ce",
        "recipient": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934cc",
        "question": "The Benz Patent-Motorwagen, widely regarded as the worldâ€™s first automobile, was first built in what year?",
        "answer": "1885",
        "answered": true,
        "isAnonymous": true
    },
    {
        "sender": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934ce",
        "recipient": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934cc",
        "question": "What does 3 dots, 3 dashes, 3 dots mean in Morse Code?",
        "answer": "SOS",
        "answered": true
    },
    {
        "sender": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934cb",
        "recipient": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934cd",
        "question": "What do you have if you suffer from podobromhidrosis?",
        "answer": "Smelly feet",
        "answered": true,
        "isAnonymous": true
    },
    {
        "sender": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934cb",
        "recipient": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934cd",
        "question": "How many strings does a standard ukulele have?",
        "answer": "4",
        "answered": true
    },
    {
        "sender": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934cb",
        "recipient": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934ce",
        "question": "What organization grew out of the Hubbard Dianetic Research Foundation?",
        "answer": "The Church of Scientology",
        "answered": true,
        "isAnonymous": true
    },
    {
        "sender": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934cd",
        "recipient": "56cb91bdc3464f14678934ce",
        "question": "On the standard Monopoly board, what color are the Chance cards?",
        "answer": "Orange",
        "answered": true
    }
]